careeraddict.com 2019-11-12

# Privacy Policy | CareerAddict

This Privacy Policy is applicable for the CareerAddict.com and its subdomains (hereinafter ‘CareerAddict’). We appreciate your interest in our websites, products, and services and we value the importance of protecting your privacy and personal data. To ensure transparency and security, our Privacy Policy as set forth below will inform you about the nature, scope and purpose of the personal data processed by us.

#### WHAT IS PERSONAL DATA

Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. CareerAddict collects, processes, or uses personal data, if you provide it to us and give us your consent. Personal data may include name, age, email, phone, address, job title, profession and other data that you have provided while registering on our websites, contacting us, or applying to receive our services using the contact forms, registration forms, or other service related forms on our websites.

For the best user experience and to improve our websites and services, we also collect data sent by your web browser, e.g., information about your browser, your IP address, and your operating system.

#### WHY DO WE NEED YOUR PERSONAL DATA

When you use services provided on CareerAddict websites, you may be asked to provide certain personal information. We will store this personal data and hold it on computers or otherwise. We will use this data in the following ways:

  * To register you with CareerAddict websites and provide services where you have registered to receive them. You can unsubscribe from these services and delete your account with CareerAddict at any time; 
  * To provide you with information about new products and services and special offers we think you will find valuable; 
  * To answer any queries which you may send to us by CareerAddict internal mail, external e-mail or our customer support system; 
  * In order to conduct customer satisfaction and related surveys for improvement of our services;
  * To improve the security of our websites;
  * To meet our legal compliance obligations;
  * For crime prevention and detection purposes;
  * If you have consented to it, we may inform you about new products and services and special offers of selected third parties; 
  * Beyond these purposes, we process your data only if you have granted express consent for its stated purposes. 

#### TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We do not sell, or trade your personal data to third parties. When you use CareerAddict and our services, you decide for yourself, how much contact or other personal information you wish to display.

We may give information about you as follows:

  * We may provide our third party service providers and processors with access to your personal information. These services providers may include: credit or debit card processing companies; our customer support centre; marketing organizations, who may market and promote our services; internet service providers who provide internet connection and host our facilities; consumer research companies that assist us with understanding consumer interests by conducting surveys. We only share your personal information to the extent required for the performance of required by you services. We implemented safeguards to ensure that our service providers treat personal information in a way that is consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy and that it is never used except to fulfill our services to our users. We may also disclose your personal information as permitted or required by law. For example, we will disclose personal information to those governmental bodies, who have authority to obtain it, in order to comply with a warrant or subpoena issued by a court of a competent jurisdiction, and to comply with record production requirements. 
  * Our websites may also include social media features (e.g., share or like buttons). Such features are provided by third-party social media platforms such as LinkedIn, Twitter, or Facebook. Where data is collected this way, its processing is governed by the privacy policy of the respective social media platforms. 
  * Our content may link to third party websites to provide relevant references. We are not responsible for such external content, which may contain separate privacy policies and data processing disclosures. 
  * In the event of sale of all or substantial part of the assets of DeltaQuest Media, we may transfer personal information in our control to a third party purchaser that agrees to use personal information for the same reasons as identified in this Privacy Policy. 
  * To our employees and agents to do any of the above on our behalf, now or in the future.

If you choose not to provide certain personal information we request, you will still be able to visit CareerAddict websites, but you may be unable to access some functionality or services offered by CareerAddict. 

#### YOUR CONSENT

By choosing to provide us with your personal information you are consenting to its use in accordance with the principles outlined in this Privacy Policy and as outlined at the time you are asked to provide any personal information. We may contact you by e-mail or otherwise in order to provide you with updates pertaining to the services, as well as information about additional offers, products or events that we believe may be of interest to you.

#### WITHDRAWING YOUR CONSENT

We provide you with a way to withdraw your consent for any of the communications received by you via external e-mail or otherwise. If you have given us your email for purposes of communication or promotion, we will use your data to contact you or send promotional emails relating to your interests. You may revoke your consent to being contacted by email for promotional purposes any time, by clicking on an unsubscribe link or replying directly stating your wish to unsubscribe.

#### CHILDREN AND EDUCATION

We understand the importance of taking extra precautions to protect the privacy and safety of children using the CareerAddict websites and services. Children under the age of 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, are not permitted to use our websites and services, unless their parent provided verifiable consent.

If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13, or equivalent minimum age depending on the jurisdiction, without verifiable parental consent, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

If at any time parents need to access, correct, or delete data associated with their child's information, they may contact our Customer Support Centre by following ‘Contact us’ link provided at the footer or header on each page of CareerAddict websites.

#### TECHNICAL AND ORGANIZATIONAL DATA PROTECTION

CareerAddict implements commercially reasonable technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data against abuse and loss. We store such data in secure environments. We provide training to our employees on data protection best practices and require them to enter into a confidentiality agreement.

While we use all reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your data submitted through our websites.

#### COOKIES

When you visit CareerAddict, our system automatically collects information about your visit, such as your browser type, your IP address, and the referring website. This collection may be done in conjunction with our vendors and partners (see data processors list below). We may receive from them general demographic or usage data of our site visitors. We do not use automatically collected information to identify you personally without collecting additional consent.

Such information is typically collected using web cookies, web or email pixels (also known as beacons), embedded hyperlinks, and similar tools. All commonly used browsers can generally be set to disable or delete individual cookies. See below for the types of cookies we use and their respective purposes.

_Required Cookies:_ enable the navigation and basic functionality of the websites, e.g., access to protected areas of our websites.

_Functional Cookies:_ allow us to analyze your website usage and your selections on the website (e.g. your login name, language, or region), so we can save these settings and offer you a more personalized experience.

_Advertising Cookies:_ allow us to better assess the effectiveness of our content marketing and advertising efforts. These cookies are provided by our third-party partners to analyze and track site visit and signups stemming from advertising. We do not share your personal information (such as name or email) to third-party providers outside of site visit data collected directly by such Advertising Cookies, though your site visit data may be linked with other personal information collected elsewhere by such third-party providers. Such external data processing is governed by the privacy policies of these third-party providers.

See below for descriptions about the cookies used on our websites and how you can opt out from them.

Our website uses [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/), a web analysis service of Google, Inc. (“Google”). Learn more from their [Terms of Service](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Opt-out: Download the browser plugin “Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on” [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Our website uses [Google AdWords](https://adwords.google.com/) Conversion Tracking cookie to measure and optimize the performance and user experience related to our ads in Google Search or selected Google Display Network sites. Learn more about Google’s privacy policy [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Opt-out: Visiting [Google’s Ads Settings.](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)

#### Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative's multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at marketing@careeraddict.com and contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

#### TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Some parties that process or store personal information may be located in jurisdictions outside your country of residence. Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in these jurisdictions and, as a result, foreign governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through the laws in these countries.

#### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on CareerAddict websites, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of external e-mail or otherwise. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected. You agree that by using the CareerAddict websites you are expressly and affirmatively consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive e-mails, and other communications as described above.

#### COMPLAINTS RESOLUTION

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. As a user of the CareerAddict websites, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the CareerAddict websites, the Internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the CareerAddict websites.

We are committed to providing a fair and responsive system for handling and resolving complaints concerning the handling of personal information. You have a right to complain and to have your complaint handled efficiently if you are concerned about our handling of your personal information. Upon request, our Data Protection Officer will provide you with information as to whether and what personal data we store in relation to you. Should your personal data be incorrect, you may have it rectified. You may also revoke your consent to use your personal data in the future, in whole or in parts, or request deletion of your personal data. We believe that any complaint that we may receive is a valuable opportunity to improve the services that we deliver to you and to maintain your confidence in our services. If at any time you wish to lodge a complaint in respect of the handling, use or disclosure of your personal information by us, you may do so by contacting our Customer Support Centre by using our ‘Contact Page’.

Last revised 24th of May 2018
